<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Open Data 500</title><link href="http://localhost:8000/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://localhost:8000/feeds/kr.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://localhost:8000/</id><updated>2015-06-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>Open Data 500 Korea</title><link href="http://localhost:8000//en/kr/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-06-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name></name></author><id>tag:localhost:8000,2015-06-11:en/kr/</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;About this Project&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open Data 500 Korea is a joint project between
&lt;a href="http://www.thegovlab.org/"&gt;Govlab&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.nia.or.kr/"&gt;NIA&lt;/a&gt; to conduct
a comprehensive, internationally comparable study of private sector entities
using open data in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Study Objectives&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a basis for assessing the economic and social value of open data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encourage the development of new open data companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foster a dialogue between government and the private sector on how open data
  can be made more useful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Approach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Open Data 500 Korea study will facilitate the identification, analyzation,
and organization of private sector entities using open data into a network to
enable increased communication and interaction with government to improve open
data policies. This network will be supported by Open Data Korea Forum and will
integrate with their existing community. The outcome of this project, the Open
Data 500 Korea, will be launched during the 2015 Open Data Korea Forum event in
July.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project has been reported to the &lt;a href="http://www.odsc.go.kr/"&gt;Open Data Strategy
Council&lt;/a&gt; of Korea, the highest decision making body on
open data in Korea, co-chaired by the Prime Minister and is funded by the
Ministry of Government Administration and Home Affairs (MOHAGA). It is our hope
that this network will collaborate actively with partners worldwide,
particularly those within the Open Data 500 Global Network, to bring the
benefits of open data beyond national borders to a global scale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Company Identification&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Open Data 500 Korea team will compile the list of companies and NGOs
through&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;outreach campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;advice from experts and professional organizations, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;additional research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results of the study will culminate in an online platform at
&lt;a href="http://www.opendata500.com/kr/kr"&gt;www.opendata500.com/kr/kr&lt;/a&gt;, which will
highlight the companies and their use of open data in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What The Study Is Not&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Open Data 500 Korea is not a rating or ranking of companies. It covers
companies and entities of different sizes and categories, using various kinds
of data. The Open Data 500 Korea is not a competition, but an attempt to give
a broad, inclusive view of the field. The study also does not provide a random
sample for definitive statistical analysis. Since this is the first thorough
scan of companies and entities in the field, it is not yet possible to
determine the exact landscape of open data companies and entities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;About the Open Data Policy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since enactment of the Open Data Law in 2013 there has been a massive increase
in the number of datasets opened up by government and the public sector. There
is increasingly a growing interest and policy need to improve our understanding
about the use and impact of open data socially and economically. The Open Data
500 Korea will complement existing government surveys on the use of open data
in Korea, which are grounded in the Open Data Law of Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Team&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(todo)&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="od500 kr"></category></entry></feed>